{
  "title": "Vedic Math Test Paper 2",
  "time": 15,
  "questions": [
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n96 + 78 + 9",
      "answer": 183
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n68 + 99 + 8",
      "answer": 184
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n78 + 89 + 9",
      "answer": 164
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n18 + 47 + 35",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n98 + 87 + 17",
      "answer": 202
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n498 + 498 + 88",
      "answer": 1084
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n378 + 388 + 9",
      "answer": 775
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n297 + 388 + 78",
      "answer": 763
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n298 + 498 + 487",
      "answer": 1283
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n378 + 98 + 899",
      "answer": 1375
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n6.8 + 2.1 + 0.8 + 5.1 + 1.2",
      "answer": 16.0
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n8.8 + 4.7 + 3.6 + 0.7 + 1.0",
      "answer": 18.8
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n5.6 + 4.5 + 9.8 + 2.1 + 1.3",
      "answer": 22.3
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n4.1 + 5.7 + 8.9 + 1.1 + 1.4",
      "answer": 21.2
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n9.6 + 1.7 + 8.3 + 1.2 + 0.5",
      "answer": 21.3
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n6.3 + 4.7 + 2.1 + 4.0 + 1.3",
      "answer": 18.4
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n8.9 + 3.3 + 2.1 + 5.8 + 1.9",
      "answer": 22.0
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n7.5 + 1.9 + 3.2 + 5.6 + 2.4",
      "answer": 20.6
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n4.3 + 8.9 + 5.4 + 1.7 + 2.1",
      "answer": 22.4
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n3.5 + 7.2 + 4.1 + 6.5 + 1.9",
      "answer": 23.2
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n8241 - 4991",
      "answer": 3250
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n9630 - 1880",
      "answer": 7750
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n5896 - 4998",
      "answer": 898
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n4513 - 1514",
      "answer": 2999
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n3750 - 1870",
      "answer": 1880
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n52471 - 17784",
      "answer": 34687
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n47586 - 17879",
      "answer": 29707
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n98176 - 89387",
      "answer": 8789
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n78769 - 59789",
      "answer": 18980
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n89292 - 69796",
      "answer": 19496
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n39 x 11",
      "answer": 429
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n76 x 11",
      "answer": 836
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n49 x 11",
      "answer": 539
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n57 x 11",
      "answer": 627
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n271 x 11",
      "answer": 2981
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n984 x 11",
      "answer": 10824
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n594 x 11",
      "answer": 6534
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n8035 x 11",
      "answer": 88385
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n1817 x 11",
      "answer": 19987
    },
    {
      "type": "fill",
      "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n4968 x 11",
      "answer": 54648
    }
  ]
}